Joey, your father's alive?
I can't believe this.
You really are father
and daughter.
You're both certified
never-say-die.
How are you really?
I'm fine, Auntie Beng.
That's not true.
You even dreamed about her.
Always remember
that a person who truly loves...
will never get tired of waiting.
Young people will like this.
It hits fast.
I'm looking forward
to our shipment later.
So, one of our brave policemen
here in Valmora
is already under your payroll.
I'll take care
of my fellow officers.
And as for those following
Berdugo...
You mean you have
active threats?
Just some small-time
competition.
If something goes wrong
with this deal,
your Lumen-X will be history
in Valmora.
Chief is just waiting
for the medico legal's result.
He said he still
has to double-check.
Double-check?
My husband's body has been
with them for so long.
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
So, what's your plan now?
Maybe I'll just talk
to Sir Tomas.
No! Do not deal with him.
Wow!
You look startled.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I want to have a new life.
That's why I need to finish
this last investment.
The transaction will take place
later, let's leave now.
Shouldn't Zoey be with you
for that?
If you don't come with me,
I won't tell your father...
that we got information.
You know, you're the only one
with contact with him.
[OBB]
Five hundred million?
Yes, and I already alerted
our unit.
Wait, are you sure
it's really Berdugo
they're transacting with?
I'm not sure yet.
But what's clear is the
transaction will happen today.
Around lunch time.
So, you're not even sure.
There was no mention of Berdugo
or the drugs.
What if it's really just their
investment meeting?
What if you don't know
anything about profiling?
So let the actual profilers
like me handle it.
What if I want to be sure?
Maybe your profiling tools
are just tarot cards
and crystal balls?
How dare you mock my profession?
Andrew, are your standards
really this low?
Standards, really?
You're the one
who gets triggered
with just one question.
Are you saying I'm insecure?
I'm saying you're overreacting.
Wait, can you guys chill out?
You two aren't even the enemies.
Can we set aside the anger
before we plan?
I don't think
there's a “we” here.
And you made a deal with us.
You know we strictly
follow protocols.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
"We strictly follow protocols."
So what?
I just asked her.
She's the one who's triggered.
How would I know
she'd get offended like that?
No reaction?
Go ahead, defend her again.
Go!
Joey, I'm not defending her.
But there's a problem.
[SUSPICIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
You can't join the operation.
What?
Why?
So last night,
I called Zoey.
I had a deal with her agency
to formalize our mission here.
And to get access
to information.
But since it's official
and government sanctioned,
civilians are not allowed.
And you, what about you?
Well, I'm included.
I'm covering the raid as media.
I'm filed.
Documented.
You are not.
Joey, if we insist
on bringing you along,
they may charge you
with obstruction of justice.
That's unfair, Andrew.
You know how much I want this.
Because I want to make sure
Berdugo gets arrested.
And I can't join?
Joey, I know.
I promise you,
I'll do whatever it takes
to make it happen.
Okay?
[SIGHS]
I will never let you down.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, you! It looks like
you're up to something.
Someone just asked for help.
They're asking if I know
anything about Berdugo.
[LINE RINGS]
[PHONE RINGING]
Castro.
Boss, I already saw the people
looking for you.
What?
Send me their photos.
Yes, Boss.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[ELECTRONIC BLIPPING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Joey, I'm sorry.
Let's go.
[SIGHS]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Captain Castro.
Captain Castro!
Brent, do you still remember me?
Yes, how are you?
This is my fiancé.
Oh, we just checked in earlier.
Who are you with?
No one, just me.
Just getting some air.
If you want to hang out later,
just message me, okay?
Sure, sure.
Good to see you.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
So, Joey?
Do you want me to take you
to the bus station?
I have a car.
It's hard to commute here.
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
Why don't you go back to Zoey?
Maybe she's waiting for you.
Don't say...
I keep talking about Zoey again.
But it's true, isn't it?
You'll go back to the office
because you're going
to plan the raid.
And why don't you just admit it?
Stop pretending.
You still love her.
And you just want her
all to yourself.
All to myself?
Do you think I'm making deals
just to get rid of you
and have Zoey to myself?
[SCOFFS]
That's your problem,
you like to assume.
You just saw Zoey kiss me,
and you think
we'll get back together.
Would you kiss just to break up?
And you're just here
for your tirade, right?
And Zoey's here, too.
So, you're hitting two birds
with one stone.
And don't be shy,
you still love her.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
If there's someone
I want to be with
in this mission
and the ones to come,
it's not Zoey.
Joey, it's you.
If only it were possible.
But if you think I'd betray you
and find a way
to get rid of you...
Then fine, okay.
It's better this way.
[TRICYCLE REVVING]
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Go, your tricycle is here.
Get in.
Take care, okay?
You, too.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TRICYCLE REVVING]
[SUSPICIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop here.
Stop here, Sir.
Why, Ma'am?
Sorry, Sir.
I don't need the ride anymore.
What?
You just wasted my time.
I'm not earning from this.
I'm really sorry.
[TRICYCLE REVVING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad needs to know
about the transaction.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But what if Berdugo
doesn't show up?
Whatever happens, happens.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPICIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Your brother-in-law
really won't bring any good
to our organization.
But, Boss,
does he already know about you?
If he knows,
he won't expose himself.
He'll move covertly
so he can fish
for information from me.
So, it doesn't seem like it yet.
But, Boss, you should leave
before Andrew sees you.
Where are you now?
I'm already in Valmora too,
Boss.
A few minutes from the resort.
The items?
Are they ready?
All good, Boss.
Ready for dispatch.
Good.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Listen, everybody.
150,000 Lumen-X pills
are on their way to Valmora
as we speak.
But we need
to produce 300,000 more
to deliver to three more
regions!
Can we do it?
Yes, Ma'am.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Theresa.
How many times
do I have to tell you
to stop calling me that name?
That name doesn't exist anymore.
My name is Liza!
L-I-Z-A!
Liza.
Okay?
Okay.
So, when do I meet
your business partner, Berdugo?
You do not meet him
when you want.
He meets you when he wants.
I didn't agree to join here
to be a nobody.
[SCOFFS]
Join?
As far as I know,
you're still not fully inside.
You still haven't told me
where we can find that girl
who filmed me
and who keep messing around
with our operations
with her crew.
Who?
Joey?
Yes.
I need details.
I already told you.
I don't know them.
We just crossed paths
because I was looking for you.
Jin Ho,
coincidence doesn't exist
in my world.
Look around you.
Every single person in this room
earns their spot here.
No exception.
Not even you.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Quick rundown
of do's and don'ts, Andrew.
One, you stay behind my line.
Two, no independent contact
with the target.
If you need something, tell me
or your assigned escort.
Three, no outside comms.
No info goes out...
to anyone, to any agency.
Even to the police?
Especially to the police.
We protect our intel
for a reason.
Okay, everyone, listen up.
Mr. Andrew Dizon will be
covering our raid
as media observer.
He's authorized.
His presence in
the operation is valid.
As of this hour,
three back-up units
are arriving from Region IV.
This is a major operation.
The meet-up is high-value.
Target site.
Here is Berdugo's villa.
This is where the drug deal
will happen.
Where are you, Berdugo?
We are working with a theory
that their deal
is with Berdugo.
Berdugo?
I used to read about him
in intel briefings in NCR.
There's still
no visual on him, right?
No ID.
No fingerprints.
Yes, none.
Actually, he's like an urban
legend...
but feared.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I can't believe this!
This is the first time
we're meeting face to face.
You know what?
I don't believe
you suddenly have a meeting
with your foreign clients.
You know what I smell?
Those people looking for you,
are they your problem?
You know what, Berdugo?
You are a very powerful man.
But I,
I have my networks too.
And when word gets out
that your operation
is in danger...
you will look weak.
And when that happens,
the market will collapse.
If we lose our clients' trust,
sales will go down.
You will lose money.
Are you threatening me?
No.
Just stating facts.
[VEHICLES REVVING]
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
[LINE BEEPING]
I'll talk to you later.
Bastard...
Matias, where are you?
Boss, we're here.
Have you left?
No, I'm staying.
But, Boss...
It's okay.
But let's finish this.
We have bigger clients waiting.
Copy, Boss.
[PHONE BLIPS]
Tell Delilah I'm staying.
But tell her
to compose herself
before she faces me.
I have no patience
for emotional breakdowns
or people who collapse
under pressure.
Yes, I'll tell her, Berdugo.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You, bring all of that inside.
You two, take position
here later.
Do you understand?
Yes, Boss.
Matias.
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
Go on.
Let's go.
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Tell everyone...
to take their positions.
Copy, Sir.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What's that?
Sir, please check.
Madame Delilah's orders
for the guest.
Bring it in,
then leave immediately.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
By the way, I want to apologize
for my little misconduct
earlier.
It's just that
the gentleman's agreement
is very important to me.
You know, for a new partnership.
That's why I'm still here,
Delilah.
Oh, I almost forgot.
[SNAPS]
Earlier, I let my temper speak.
I hope this time
I'll make it right.
Do you mind?
There you go.
That's much better.
Now, you look like a man
that people should fear.
I must say...
you have good taste.
Oh, bet I do...
especially with partners.
By the way,
is this your trusted guy?
Well, we need to talk.
Because next time,
I'll be speaking to you.
But of course, if you permit,
Berdugo.
Certainly.
Well, let's seal the deal then.
Cheers to new a partnership.
New partnership.
[GLASS CLINKS]
As I was saying...
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
Banjo.
It's fine.
Shoes can be cleaned.
I'm terribly sorry.
Well, shall we start then?
- Let's.
- Please, sit down, gentlemen.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Oh, I just remembered something.
I have to do something.
Excuse me.
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
Boss, Andrew is still
here for sure.
It's risky, he might catch you.
I'm not the only one
who should be careful.
You should too.
He knows you too, right?
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
What's going on here, Matias?
So, you know each other?
Matias is my business partner.
That's why we need
to hurry this up.
But this woman looks like
she's stalling.
Well, sorry about that.
I was having some steaks
prepared for you, guys.
Would you rather have medium
rare or well-done?
I would prefer you hurry up
and start the transaction.
I don't like wasting time.
Come on.
You're in such a hurry.
Why is that?
Could it be those people
chasing you?
I told you,
they're just small fry
competition.
Well, small fry or not,
we need to be safe.
So, you don't have
to worry about it.
I already told my men
to go after them
and eliminate them.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I thought they were small fry?
You still have time
to change, Francis!
Surrender now!
You're the ones
who should surrender!
You entered the wrong den!
I picked this up
when Berdugo was escaping.
Sir Tomas...
is a very private person,
isn't he?
Even I don't know
everything he does.
It's a spy camera.
I have someone to catch.
Tell them who you really are.
I want you
to tell them everything!
Brother, is that blood?
I wanted to tell you something.
What's the problem?